<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Markus Barthlen</title>
    <link>https://MarkusBarthlen.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Markus Barthlen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 22:18:20 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://MarkusBarthlen.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Best Books I read in 2020</title>
      <link>https://MarkusBarthlen.github.io/posts/books2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 22:18:20 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://MarkusBarthlen.github.io/posts/books2020/</guid>
      <description>Best books I read in 2020  Almanack of Naval Ravikant by Eric Jorgenson  Easy to read and full of good quotes. I especially loved the parts about happiness. You might not even recognize that happiness is a valid goal in life. And it can have enormous impact on other aspects of your life. It&amp;rsquo;s free https://www.navalmanack.com. The best book I&amp;rsquo;ve ever read.
Oxygen by Nick Lane  A tremendous book that will change your perspective on cell biology and possibly make you think about how you can live your life to better protect your cells.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Impressum</title>
      <link>https://MarkusBarthlen.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 21:04:52 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://MarkusBarthlen.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>This is the blog of Markus Barthlen.
Markus Barthlen
Markenbildchenweg 23-25
D-56068 Koblenz +49 1515 4168580
VAT ID Germany: DE343647130 Please note that international consulting is not planned, but contact me if you are interested and we can work something out.
Contact me at wichtig (at) barthlen.de
Please note that electronic communication is not failsafe. If you want secure communication please use postal mail.
The content of this internet presence has been curated carefully.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Impressum</title>
      <link>https://MarkusBarthlen.github.io/gdpr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 21:04:52 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://MarkusBarthlen.github.io/gdpr/</guid>
      <description>Data protection I take the protection of personal data very seriously. Therefore, I keep confidentiality subject to German and EU law and to this declaration.
General and required information Responsible for this website Responsible for this website is:
Markus Barthlen
Markenbildchenweg 23-25
D-56068 Koblenz +49 1515 4168580
wichtig (at) barthlen.de
What are your rights? You have the right to get information about the data saved by me, to correct errors, to delete the data, to block the data from being processed and to oppose the processing of data.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
